## Nathan Atherton

Currently living in North West UK Tel: 07584032425

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nathan-atherton/ Email: nathanatherton2@gmail.com

#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Currently in my final semester of my Web Design and Development degree, prior to this a 15-month long apprenticeship in Marketing and Graphic and Design Media was completed. I have had a lot of experience in technology and keeping up to date with the latest new releases that are related to computers specifically. I have previously built a PC with the specs of 8GB Memory, a GTX 980Ti GPU, and an intel i5-3750k CPU. I have previously been consistent with editing videos and creating thumbnails and logos, these were then implemented on YouTube. I have also been involved in game testing, testing a game named 'Iron fish' which was released as a full PC Indie game.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

September 2016 – Present Predicted Grade 1st

Web Design and Development Edge Hill University

June 2016 – July 2016 Grade – Pass Edge Hill Fastrack Edge Hill University

November 2014 - February 2016 Edexcel Level 3 Diploma in Create and Digital Media (QCF)

Versa Ltd

Edexcel BTEC Level 3 Certificate in Creative and Digital Media (QCF)
Versa Ltd

September 2013 – October 2014 2 AS Levels Deanery Sixth Form Wigan

September 2008 – July 2013 10 GCSE's above grade C Deanery C of E High School Wigan

# November 2014 – February 2016 SKILLS

- Adobe Premiere Pro Video Editing
- Adobe Photoshop Photo Editing
- Adobe Illustrator Vector Drawings
- Sony Vegas Video Editing
- Adobe After Effects Video Editing
- SAP Software
- HTML Coding

- CSS Coding
- JavaScript Coding
- PHP Coding
- Advanced Microsoft Word
- Advanced Microsoft Excel
- Advanced Microsoft PowerPoint

#### **CAREER SUMMARY**

#### May 2016 - Present

McDonald's

Crew Member

- Leading a kitchen of at least 5 people, ensuring that all food is cooked to the highest of quality.
- Cooking food in a fast manner to meet customer expectations

- Spoken to customers and correctly taken their orders
- Handled cash from customers when orders have been taken

#### November 2014 - February 2016

Versa Ltd

Marketing Apprentice

- Created designs for advertisements
- Created line drawings of products, such as benches and bike shelters
- File Management
- Managing the company Social Media accounts
- Writing Blog Posts

### **July 2012 – July 2012**

Heinz

Work Experience

- Organised Spreadsheets
- Used purchasing system
- Created engineering jobs on internal system

#### **INTERESTS**

I am interested in keeping up to date with football, I enjoy attending football matches in my spare time, I support Wigan Athletic and have followed this team throughout all my life. Another of my interests that I do partake in during my free time is that I follow esports, the main game that is involved in the esports that I follow is called Rocket League.

REFERENCES ARE AVAILABLE ON REQUEST